const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '10を10でわった数は？', answer: '1', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '100を10でわった数は？', answer: '10', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '300を10でわった数は？', answer: '30', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '8000を10でわった数は？', answer: '800', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '450を10でわった数は？', answer: '45', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '9630を10でわった数は？', answer: '963', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '77320を10でわった数は？', answer: '7732', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '9040を10でわった数は？', answer: '904', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '100500を10でわった数は？', answer: '10050', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '203000を10でわった数は？', answer: '20300', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];